let's look at the answer to our temporal
locality quiz in this code the question
was which of these memory locations have
temporal locality and the choices were J
sum and the elements of our temporal
locality says that once we access a
memory location we are likely to access
it again for the variable J this is true
we are using it here here here in every
iteration of the loop so the first time
we access it if we conclude that it will
be accessed again soon we would be right
actually once we begin accessing it is
going to be accessed a lot it's going to
be accessed to initialize it to check if
it's less than a thousand to access the
array to increment it to check to access
to increment many many times so this
variable definitely does have temporal
locality the variable sum same thing it
is being initialized and then in every
iteration of this loop it is going to be
read so that we can add something to it
and then written back to memory so this
definitely also has temporal locality
once we access it we can conclude that
it will be accessed soon again for each
element of the array are however and
note that the array has many many memory
locations we do not have temporal
locality element are of zero once it's
accessed in the loop that's the only
time we access in this loop we will
access our of one out of two etc but for
each element it's accessed only once so
if we conclude that when it's accessed
it's going to be accessed again soon we
would not be correct so this choice
should not be selected this variable
does not have temporal locality in this
code